

## Contact

lymanwong.github.io

**\( (415) 509-1409** 

in lymanwong

lymanwong

## **Education**

San Francisco State University Bachelor of Arts Biology

## **Skills**

**SKILLS**: HTML5, JavaScript, jQuery, WordPress, Git, Agile Development, Jira, Sass/Less, Heroku, Bootstrap, CSS

# **Summary**

My goal is to leverage my 3+ years of client-facing experience, community management skills, and expertise with my 2+ years of Front-End experience in the tech industry into a full-time Front-End position where I can continue to learn and grow.

# **Employment**

#### Hack · Community Manager

- Created MVP for Hack's web application using
- Created Google Tag Manager triggers to monitor website interactions
- Used Git and Sublime Merge to deploy learning content
- Created responsive news feed using HTML5 and CSS
- Wrote teaching curriculum for the Web including Bootstrap and HTML/CSS
- Added responsive pages and updated content using the Shopify API
- Migrated website from Shopify to Wix
- Created responsive email templates on Mailchimp
- Wrote blog content explaining Javascript concepts using Markdown/HTML
- UI/UX bug fixing
- Used Phabricator to track development tasks

#### Freelance · Web Developer

- Add new features or improve UX for Squarespace and Wordpress sites
- Created a Wordpress marketing site for GameWithMe
- Implemented an SEO plan for TasteWithKevin.com
- Built new pages and updated site content as needed for TasteWithKevin.com
- Provided UI/UX design guidance
- Investigate technologies/techniques and propose the best solutions
- · Light project management

#### **Udacity** · Student Experience Specialist

Jan. 2018 to Dec. 2018

Dec. 2018 to Feb. 2019

Apr. 2019 to Current

- Created School of Business Content Marketing site based on Sketch wireframes
- Worked closely with multiple stakeholders to design the website layout
- Updated and published Digital Marketing program content using Markdown and Coco
- Refactored and run Python scripts for student enrollment verification
- Implemented Zapier tasks to increase team efficiency
- · Used Jira to manage development tasks

#### LeEco US · Web Developer

July 2016 to July 2017

- Created multiple responsive LeEco.com and LeEco.com/Chinese pages from wireframes
- Built LeEco US and India WordPress sites from wireframes
- Integrated new company header, a footer with region selector, Google Analytics, Optimize, and Tag Manager
- Improved UI/UX using vanilla JS and jQuery
- · Updated site content, conducted cross-browser testing, and bug fixing
- Assisted Front-End team to build an internal tool using React Material UI
- Use Git (version control) and worked on 1-week sprints/Agile development

# **Projects**

#### GameWithMe Blog

Wordpress Marketing site for GameWithMe

#### **School of Business Content Marketing Site**

HTML, CSS, JS, Hubspot

#### NY Times API Book Search

Made with PHP, AJAX, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap and HTML/CSS

### My Angular Profile and Blog Site

My personal website made with Angular, jQuery, Bootstrap, HTML and CSS.

#### Pinteresting

A Pinterest clone made with Rails 4.2, PostgreSQL database, and image hosting using AWS.